ingles-markets.com 2013-05-02

# Ingles Markets - Grocery Stores, Supermarkets, Pharmacies

Our postal address is

Post Office Box 6676  
Asheville, NC 28816  
(828) 669-2941

This privacy statement covers the site www.ingles-markets.com. Because Ingles Markets, Inc wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users' privacy, we have agreed to disclose our Web site information practices.

  1. What personally identifiable information Ingles Markets, Inc collects.
  2. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.
  3. What organization collects the information.
  4. How Ingles Markets, Inc uses the information.
  5. With whom Ingles Markets, Inc may share user information.
  6. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
  7. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Ingles Markets, Inc control.
  8. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

### What We Collect

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the visitor's domain and IP address.

We collect only the domain name and IP address, browser/operating system specs, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail or online contact forms, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact our Customer Service department by using out online Contact Form, calling, or writing us at the address above.

### Information Collection and Use

**Information Collection**

Ingles Markets, Inc is the sole owner of the information collected on www.ingles-markets.com. Ingles Markets, Inc collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site:

**Order**

We request information from the user on our Bakery order form and our Investor Packet Request form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, phone, and shipping address). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.

**Contact**

We request information from the user on our Customer Service Contact and Contact The Webmaster forms. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and loaction). This information is used for contact purposes and to resolve any complaints, comments, or questions the user contacted us with.

**Information Packet Request**

We request information from the user on our Information Packet Request form. A user must provide contact information so that we may mail the information packet.

**Tools For Schools**

We request information from the user on our Tools For School card link page. This information is used to link a user's Advantage Card with a chosen school. The information collected is used for processing the request and confirmation.

**Ask Leah**

We request information from the user on our Ask Leah page. This information is used so that Leah may respond directly to the user for clarification, questions, or confirmation.

**Profile**

We store information that we collect through cookies, sessions, and/or log files to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. This collected information is not tied to the users personally identifiable information. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site, to assess popular areas of our site, and determine ways to improve the site for users. We do not share your profile with other third parties. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. [How to remove cookies in Internet Explorer 6](http://support.microsoft.com/default.aspx?scid=kb;EN-US;q283185)

We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, and track paths through our site to learn about what pages are more popular. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to place Bakery orders. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. See the "Profile" section.

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Communications from the Site

**Customer Service**

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.

**Order Processing**

When users place orders with us, contact us for information, or contact us to leave comments, they will receiv automatic responses via email generated by our server, acknowledging their submission.

### Sharing

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information. Specifically, we disclose aggregate information about the numbers of visitors to our site, frequency of visits, and usage of various parts of the site.

**These are the instances in which we will share users' personal information:**

We DO NOT Share Personal Information with Third Parties, except when required by law.

### Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Ingles Markets, Inc., are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email and by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days. 

©2004 Ingles Markets, Inc

Last modified June, 2004
